

+39 339 5801878





**23/08/1987** 



Born in Foggia, maker with a background in the e-commerce and online advertising (Facebook and Instagram).

After my experience in Lisbon, as a Customer Service Representative, I deepened my studies on User Experience, becoming UX/UI Design.



### **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND**

Master in UX/UI Design on Start2impact University, from 2021 until 2022;

Bachelor's degree in Letters and Philosophy, with specialising in Archaeology, at University of Foggia, 2012 - Final grade 105/110;

High School Diploma in Applied Arts at Istituto d'Arte Perugini, in Foggia 2006, final grade 90/100.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Facebook Marketing Expert in Teleperformance from 2019 to 2020 (Lisbon);

Customer Service Representative Senior in Teleperformance, from 2018 to 2019 (Lisbon);

**E-commerce manager** for a personal project, from 2009 to 2018 (Italy).

### PROJECTS COMPLETED AS UX/UI DESIGNER

- · Brand Identity;
- Online medical examination booking site;
- E-commerce;
- Online courses site;
- → PORTFOLIO ONLINE

### **PROFESSIONAL SKILLS**

Figma/XD Adobe Suite Google Suite Miro HTML e CSS

#### **LANGUAGES**

### ITALIAN (MOTHER TONGUE)

Speaking Writing Listening

### **ENGLISH (B2)**

Speaking Writing Listening PORTUGUESE (B1)

Speaking Writing Listening

# **SOFT SKILLS**

 Creativity Analytics 0000 Empathy Precision Problem Solving Team Work Authonomy Flessibility Calmness Leadership

Each of my work experiences has helped me develop soft skills, which I apply in my UX/UI design work.

### MORE SPECIFICALLY

# **AS FACEBOOK MARKETING EXPERT** |

managed a client portfolio of small and medium-sized companies.

I talked to them to understand their needs; I studied their business in order to offer a product and advertising strategy that was advantageous as much as possible.

# **CONTACT WITH STAKEHOLDERS**

**DISCOVERY SELL** PROBLEM SOLVING **AUTHONOMY** 

#### AS CUSTOMER SERVICE REPRESENTATIVE **SENIOR** I learned to listen to the problems of

customers and users, from all touch points of the purchase path (on site and off site) and at the return phase. I helped the new agents with their first tasks

and in times of difficulty.

### 

**ACTIVE AND EMPATHIC LISTENING** 

PROBLEM SOLVING

**TEAM WORK** 

**PRECISION** 

**LEADERSHIP** 





**.** 23/08/1987

